I want to talk about truth because I feel, um, so do y'all like, why? Okay. Who in here
is still talking about voting as like a method? You know, like these people killed
another person today. Are y'all still on some, like, if we just vote the right
person, we're good. I need to know. Like, like they pop buddy right there. So are y'all still
on that? Are y'all still paying taxes? Like what, what, what actually that? No, you don't need
Malcolm X. You don't need Malcolm X. Y'all don't even, let me, let me not let y'all
work me up. Let me not let y'all work me up. So, okay. If y'all feel capable of identifying
a truth that's not in front of your face. So this is a dumb question. Why wouldn't we
need a leader that actually comes outside and aids us? Do you see an individual leader
in Minnesota who say that? Have y'all even know what Malcolm X did? That's the, that's
the comedy for me. People be running Malcolm X's name all the time, acting as if Malcolm
X was, you know, out here leading marches. Like Malcolm X, like, I always see this. I
always see this. Like Malcolm X is, you know, first of all, Malcolm X was able to be assassinated
because folks wasn't messing with Malcolm X. So let's start there. All right. That's why
he was able to be assassinated. Malcolm X wasn't doing marches and getting arrested.
What are y'all talking about? Malcolm X was, was with the nation. Malcolm X was strolling
up with the nation, with the FOI, the fruit of Islam, an organized, militarized, trained
force. Malcolm X wasn't at the Montgomery boycott. Malcolm X, he was doing something else. So
like, I just need everybody to like, understand that y'all be making up romanticized versions
of things. And it's really not helpful to you, which is why I said truth matters. Because
even the concept of the Black Panthers has been disrep, misrepresented, disrepresented, et
cetera. And when you all talk about the past, so often you're doing so without regarding the
fact that we have covered an immense amount of ground technologically in terms of changes
and shifts. Say her name is reserved for Black women killed by the police. Stop saying that in
alignment with Renee Goode. Stop. Say her name was created, a movement created by Professor
Kimberly Crenshaw in the wake of Breonna. Okay. So like, cut it out. Breonna Taylor. So please.
Truth matters. Truth matters. These things matter. And I'm going to tell you particularly why they
matter. Because we live in a time where the distruth, where the falsehoods are actively being weaponized
against you. So when you know something is being used against you, it has to become your commitment
your imperative. Your imperative are presented the way that they are meant to be. Get this
FBA bullshit out of my comments. All that foundational Black American FBA shit, that's FBI. That was
created by a nigga who don't give a fuck about Black people. Really thinks that they have the ability
to read between the lines. One of the things that's happening is so many folks are
genuinely
tied to a false sense of security that prevents them from being able to take the next step forward.
Like when I see people say like, this is why we have to vote for, you lost me. The minute you say,
this is why we have to vote for, you've lost me. You've lost me. Anyone who still believes in
electoral politics in 2026, I'm looking at you confused. In 2026, the year of the old gods and
the new, I'm genuinely like, how? How can you still consider electoral politics to be a system
that is of use for change? The question becomes, well then what do we do? Well, I am a very big believer
that when you identify effective, you then have to look at, well, what makes that system function?
And once you identify what makes that system function, you then have to figure out how to
deplete or demolish those things that make the system function. This is not a world that always had
capitalism, how new capitalism is, how new you are. Oh my, I don't want, do not, I don't want to see
nothing in here about Democrats. I don't want to see nothing in here about Democrats. Because I need y'all
to stop thinking that Democrats are anything. Please. Like I'm holding my titties. Please.
Please. Please. Stop. Oops, someone said tone it down. Blocked. Get out of here. Like, please. Ask yourself
Constitution and the Bill of Rights come from. No, because you've been told that it came from
these guys who got together and put it together. What I said about Kiki Palmer was insane. She's been
an example of hard work that pays off. The fuck did I say about Kiki Palmer? Think about this. I want you
to really think about this. Tonight, I want you to go to sleep thinking about this. I want you to ask
yourself genuinely how much of what you have been told recently has been the truth, okay? Then I want you to ask
yourself how much of what you were taught about the last 60 years was true, right?
I want you to ask yourself that. How much about the last 60 years has been true, right? Because what
happens is you've been told something and then like 20 years later you find out like, oh dang, that's not
how that happened. So do you think, honestly, that if what you've been told in the last 12 months wasn't true
and that what you haven't and what you've been told in the last 60 years, majority of it wasn't true,
do you honestly think that anything told to you by this country's controlled media by its controlled
systems are the truth? Now what I want you to do is ask yourself this question. I hope you're writing
these down. Why would people in power want people who don't have power to know the truth
of their efforts? I want these questions to be used as an exercise because you are going to be
bombarded with falsehoods. You are currently being bombarded with falsehoods and it is going to require
you to be fearless because in order for you to know the truth, you're going to have to understand that
you're not safe. And that's the lie that you've been telling yourself. And it's the lie they've been
telling you that you're safe. That these people who are in positions of power care about you,
so if you know that they're not telling you the truth, they're not really caring about you.
The lie that we tell ourselves is that they're not that bad. They can't be that bad.
Even when it's staring us in the face, you're going to have to see the truth for what it is.
And it's going to be scary. I saw a man shot and killed today. Not all these people, smart people.
The reason this is so imperative is because when you are an educator, right? And someone turns in a paper
and it exceeds their capabilities, you immediately know that someone else aided them.
You immediately know they didn't do this themselves. This is an imperative piece to resistance.
Understanding that the people that y'all keep blaming are not the ones running the show.
They're the ones carrying it out. Roland Martin doesn't want me on his show because Roland Martin
is still out here simping for Democrats. Roland Martin owes me a fucking apology because I've been
a real one saying the real shit while the whole time these motherfuckers called it harm reduction
instead of saying, yo, are you niggas going to actually do something to stop this? But they can't.
They can't do nothing to stop this because they're run and paid for by the same people.
So no, I will not be going on Roland Martin's show because these people have spent years.
And I'm pissed about it because I was one of the people being convinced that we got to be Democrats.
We got to question my research and speak to people outside of the black infosphere and understand
now hold on now. This is not, this is not for us. We are being used.
We're not being useful. We're being used. Angela Rye, we can't, we can't tell people not to push a
genocide because then we'll end up getting a president who's going to be really bad for us.
I mean, I just, I, whew. I should have put flour in that and made a stock out of it. God damn it.
This whole thing has been an exercise in bamboozlement since its beginning. The United States
began as a bamboozle, as an exercise in bamboozlement. And we are only now at a point
where there's enough information for people to be able to now put things together. And this is why
TikTok is now owned by a Zionist. This is why they're all saying the same thing about Zionism,
which is we got to get folks to stop looking at the internet because they're, they're really
realizing that Zionism is a bad thing. Yeah. And it's been running the show since day one.
It may have been called something different. Did you get bamboozled in Christianity? Absolutely.
Absolutely. Yes. None of this is pure. And that's the key thing that not enough of us are
understanding. None of this is pure. Therefore you have to fortify yourself. There you go. Tyrant for
colorant needs to happen is happening in Minnesota. It is a leaderful movement. It is a leaderful
movement. It is people who are out there, not because someone told them to be, but because their
spirit told them to be. That's why they're out there because their spirit and soul said, I should
be out here. Yeah, I should be out here. Not because the 92% said so or not to not know because
they said that's what I should be. And all those white people who are out there and anybody else who
felt to the, who felt they should join them. I'm, I am praying. I am sending them energy. I am speaking
into existence, their protection, all of the things. I love when people say, well, you ain't outside.
I just did a free book tour. I just did a free book tour where I went all around this goddamn
country and spoke into the spirit for free. So give me a fucking break. You ain't never
on a front line. Malcolm X quote unquote out there. Y'all be in your minds. Malcolm X is a Black
Panther. That's how people imagine Malcolm X in people's minds. Malcolm X is a Black Panther.
I'm like, everything you've seen about Malcolm X is him speaking at a podium or him speaking
on an interview. And then they'll come and say to me, you ain't doing shit. You can't see
the other comments because Instagram considers me a extremist. I saw someone say that we're living
in, in the twilight zone. They're taking down the signs about slavery from the parks department.
The twilight zone is the portion of time that we've been living in where the country even bothered to
pretend it wasn't racist. That is the twilight zone. The rest of this time is what this country
actually is and what it has been seeking to be from its inception. Those of us who grew up in the
80s and 90s, we got to grow up in the twilight zone. Millennials grew up in a twilight zone. We got to
grow up at a time where Blackness was everywhere. Like somehow we like slid through a wrinkle in time
and that wrinkle is closed. I was on Insecure and I remember doing an interview and someone was like,
you know, I feel like we're in a Black renaissance. I was like, why? They're like, because there's so
much Black television. I'm like, what are you talking about? I was like, because you're interviewing
me and I'm on a Black TV show? I'm on a Black TV show and when we do our read-throughs,
the writers have to laugh so loud at every joke because all of the executives are white people,
maybe aside from one or two, but all of the decision-making executives are white people
and so they have to laugh extra loud at the jokes because those people don't understand the humor of
the show because they're literally not Black. I've not always known this country was fascist.
This is another farce that we need to get clear. Black people in this country have not thought or
existed as a monolith ever, ever. There have always been Black folks who are advancing
the effort of fascism and there have always been Black folks who say, shh, we see the fascism, but
you doing too much. They killed that man in cold blood today. But you know what? I live in New York
and they let that man, Daniel Penny, kill that houseless man on that train in cold blood because
this is a cold-blooded place. This is a cold-blooded place. Don't lie to yourself. Don't lie to yourself
like you're able to just, like you aren't able to just walk by houseless people and drive by
houseless people and not care nothing. Like, if we're gonna be talking about truth, like, keep it a buck.
You feel me? Keep it a buck now. This is a cold-ass place. And people sat there and watched that nigga
kill Jordan Neely because he was talking loud. Do you even think twice when you see a houseless
person outside? Who used to be so bothered by how bothered I was about others? This used to really
annoy him. Like, oh my god. This is a cold-ass place. This is a cold-ass place. How are you gonna warm it up?
Hmm? Like, for a second, I really got in my head because it was like, damn, like, they really
murked buddy today and I'm overhearing my feelings. Man, F your feelings, Amanda. And then I remembered, no.
No, because my feelings are what have kept me from being able to stay indoctrinated. So, my feelings do matter.
And I gotta protect them. And that's what made me come on here to talk to y'all. You should be horrified
today. Oh, thanks, Ifshara. And the new movement should always be asking yourself, what would I have done?
If I was there, what would I have done? What would I have done if I was there? Would I have run when the gun went off?
What would I have done? Have I talked to my kids about what's going on?
People asking, do you think this is the beginning of a civil war? A civil war is when,
well, they'll say it's when opposing ideologies, but that's not really what it is.
It's when one group feels like they're losing power. And so, they strike up arms to retain power.
But the piece of the pie that continues to be overlooked is that there is a group above those
groups that benefits from that. And we have yet to address those people.
Y'all Catholics, let the Catholic Church keep going after they pedophiled all them kids. You know how
crazy that is? Y'all niggas kept going to church. That's crazy. That's crazy. That's crazy.
Type of shit I'm talking about. Thank you, Miranda, for what you all are doing in Minnesota.
I mean, I'm just saying, like, that's the equivalent of, like, I mean, Kamala didn't have anything to do
with the genocide. Crazy. Crazy. Minnesotans are still outside? Because I saw they had built up a
barricade with the trash cans. I'm reading the comments. Sorry. Everybody in Minneapolis,
Minneapolis, you are a testament. You are an inspiration. And for the record, they always
were. Minneapolis burnt down the precinct during George Floyd. Okay? I don't think y'all remember
that. And when we're talking about leaders, these people are not leaders who consider themselves
politicians. They're not leaders. If they was really bad about it, they would be like, you know
what? Fuck this shit. There should be shit leaking all over the place right now. Somebody talking
about we need Jesus. Do we? Where is he? Y'all keep thinking Jesus is going to come down from the
sky. If you need Jesus, then you need to activate Jesus in your body. If it's flesh of my flesh,
then he's already in you. Who is this idiot? Follow at me. Okay. I was like, why are y'all in here
charging folks to pray? Like, this is nutty. Why, why are y'all in here charging folks to pray?
Like, get, get, get, get, get. I love beverages. Thank you, Queen's arrived. Queen has arrived.
I ask myself every day, am I doing enough? Cause I, cause I honestly feel like, I feel like my,
my role in this is to figure out what to do. And, and the process of that feels like stasis.
Yes. I do. I love beverages. I don't mean drinks. I just mean beverages. I'm gonna eat this meal that
I made tomorrow. It's Sunday. On Sundays I get up and I do my 20 minutes of movement, but I do 20
minutes of like, I do a circuit, pushups, sit-ups, leg raises, sit-up, wait, pushups, sit-ups,
leg raises, and mountain climbers. Someone said, I know I'll be dead before it gets better. I won't
be. I won't be dead before it gets better. I'm gonna see it get better. I'm gonna tell you that.
I'm not claiming that. I was, I was claiming that before, but I'm not claiming that no more.
I was at the YMCA and this lady was talking about, she was going to the birthday party of
107 year old woman. Now, by the way, I'm not, I don't really want to live to 107, but I was
talking to the old ladies and they were like, yeah, I mean, they 75, they young. Do a party for
107. And then one of them said she was from South Africa and y'all it took, oof, man, it
took everything in me not to turn that conversation up. Therefore, apartheid, I had to really choose.
I had to choose peace. I had to choose peace. Cause I really could have turned it up. Y'all
it was one against foe. I could handle that one against foe. I could handle that. But I, I say,
you know, I'm a, I'm a, I'm a let it rock. I'll say, I'm a let this lady live, but I made a pact
with myself that if I catch her again, I'm a be like, so when you were living in apartheid South
Africa, what was your role? So that's, that's, that's at the ready y'all. I got that in my back
pocket. Next time I see her. Bam! Thought I was slipping, didn't you? Nope. I seen you take on 20.
Yeah. She said that, you know, cause I be in there and they don't, you know, they don't know,
they don't know the story. They don't know what it is. Someone said, how do I sustain my hope for
the future? You'll be getting what I want. And I don't want the shit to end. Don't want, I don't
want the shit to end. If enough of us collectively don't want the shit to end, then we will create
what we need to do to stop it from ending. Collective consciousness. The people in power have just
gotten a stronger collective consciousness than us. Centuries now, perfecting the unable to have
that collective consciousness. So when people ask me, like, how do you keep your hope? Cause I mean,
I've thought about it. And then I was like, no, because I like all types of nonsense. No,
I don't. So if enough of us are just like, shit, I don't want this shit to end either.
The universe conspires to give you what you need. I've been by a drug dealer by now.
Like that should have happened. If that, the odds were there, didn't happen. Wasn't my story.
Have I had terrible things happen to me? Absolutely. Absolutely. However, I know that I walk a path
of pure goodness. That's always my goal. So I have to believe that that means something.
Oh, y'all still? I'm telling you, the fact that I did not end up having a baby by a drug dealer and
having to visit the prison with the baby is, is mind boggling. Shocking. Shocking. Mind boggling.
You can only attribute that to one thing. There's a bigger purpose. There's a bigger path.
So someone said they just threw the phone. People ask dumb ass questions. Why were you ever dating
drug dealers? Cause they're sexy. They have like built in swag and they know shit that I don't know,
which is also sexy. Hello? I also grew up on nineties hip hop. Hello? Melona. Like, I mean,
it's just like, come on. Someone just asked, was it, was it New York or Cali? New York, Detroit,
the Bay, LA. I never knew anything about their business. I never was involved.
It was always like this thing they do. And I think the mystery was also very like,
how many people in here? Yeah. I had my time with a drug dealer. Yeah. You know, so have a,
I asked you all to ask yourself some questions before you go to sleep. And I want you to remember
what those questions were. The number one question is why would the people in power
allow you? No, I'm going to put it differently. Why would the people in power tell you the truth?
Why would the people in power tell you the truth? I want you to ask yourself why or how can those
who are so obviously inept carry out such a grand operation? And the third question I want you to ask
yourself is, do I understand power and control? Because I couldn't see what the fuck shit really
was until I realized that my concept of power and control was based on my own perspective. And I am
not someone who seeks power and control. So that is going to be a super limited understanding.
In order to understand the power and control being held over me, I had to expand my consciousness
of what people are looking for who seek power and control. And I can tell you, when you start to open
your mind, it is scary because you're like, what? Yes. And you have to keep pushing further to see
the expanse because your version is typically not going to be the one. I understand we have very
specific things we need to deal with in this immediate moment. Not paying taxes, not voting on an electoral
level, challenging those on a local level to either be public servants or not, creating systems of food and
mutual aid, etc. Yes. I also understand that my role is to, while we're doing that, continue expanding
the wonderment and imagination and innovation mind. Because an empire is falling and one is coming in its
place. And we cannot allow that. We cannot allow that. So I want you all to question, to ask yourself
those questions. And let me tell you, what you lose in a false sense of safety, you will gain
in courage and confidence as you push through. So Papito asks, where do we find it? The answer is to
power and control. How much do you know about the presidents of the United States? How much do you know
about the Vatican? How much do you know about the secretaries of defense of the United States?
These are people who seek power. There has been an immense amount of writing and documentaries done
on the, on these people. How much do you know about billionaires like JP Morgan? Where did the Astors
get their money? The Rothschilds, the Rockefellers? How much do you know about Queen Victoria?
About the British Empire? These are the beginning. Because when you are able to start understanding how
these people think, you begin to conceptualize how little you mean to their world. And that should
piss you the fuck off. Carnegie. Vanderbilt. You know, the show, The Gilded Age, is literally
romanticizing for you the making of the billionaire class. They're putting them in pretty dresses.
They're showing you their myopic surface frivolous arguments and, and, and trivialities. And then
you're watching it like, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. No, they're brainwashing you. All of that shit
that you're watching is not fantasy. The Gilded Age is literally about how the United States became the
next new world. That's where the billionaire class came from. I saw someone here say that's
why they have bunkers in private islands. I'm gonna tell you why I think they have bunkers in private
islands. I don't think they have bunkers in private islands because the earth is going to have a natural
disaster. I think they have bunkers in private islands because they know that we're going to rise up
and they're going to run. I think that's why they have bunkers in private islands. I don't think it's
because they're going to drop an atomic bomb. I think it's because they know that we actually do have
power. We don't know that. We don't know that. History Channel. Exactly. The men who built America.
Thank you, Fifi. We don't know that. And when you see Arab states capitulating and you see
these other countries, you know, like your man who's trying to step in in Iran. I think his name
is Pahlavi. You know, you see places like El Salvador and the guy who's trying to run shit in Honduras
and Nigeria. You see these folks. These are just folks who are like, oh, well, if they're getting in
on colonialism, then I want a piece of the pie too. That's it. That's it. They're just, they're just
bottom feeders. They're scavengers. You have to get a spiritual base. And I will tell you one last
thing. So much of what we have charted our course on to make this life make sense is about belief.
Having faith in that which we can't see. Aligning ourselves to structures of
spirit that soothe us. And I want you to know that when it comes to the connection of the human and
the earth, it does not require belief. It is very clearly recorded. When it comes to the connection
of the earth and the universe, it does not require belief. It is very finitely recorded. The Fibonacci
spiral. The mirrored images of our physical beings to that which is in nature. And when you see this,
it allows you to perhaps not abandon your beliefs, but to bolster them to something sturdy.
And what is necessary right now is sturdiness. That is where you will find your ability to grasp
the truth that you will need to understand to be effective in actually saving this place that
we've decided is worth saving because we love dolphins.